[{"question":"\u05de\u05d4\u05d5 \u05de\u05e7\u05e6\u05d5\u05e2\u05d5 \u05e9\u05dc \u05de\u05d9\u05e7\u05d9 \u05d1\u05d5\u05d2\u05e0\u05d9\u05dd?","rank":"\u05de\u05d0\u05e4\u05e8","answer":"\u05de\u05e2\u05e6\u05d1 \u05e9\u05d9\u05e2\u05e8","answers":["\u05e7\u05d5\u05e1\u05de\u05d8\u05d9\u05e7\u05d0\u05d9","\u05de\u05e2\u05e1\u05d4",2,0,1]},{"question":"\u05de\u05d4 \u05de\u05d4\u05d1\u05d0\u05d9\u05dd \u05d0\u05d9\u05e0\u05d5 \u05de\u05d5\u05ea\u05d2 \u05d8\u05d9\u05e4\u05d5\u05d7?","rank":"\u05e0\u05d9\u05d9\u05df \u05d5\u05d5\u05e1\u05d8","answer":"\u05dc\u05e0\u05e7\u05d5\u05dd","answers":["\u05e7\u05e8\u05dc\u05d9\u05d9\u05df ","\u05e8\u05d1\u05dc\u05d5\u05df",1,0,1]},{"question":"\u05de\u05d5\u05ea\u05d2 \u05d8\u05d9\u05e4\u05d5\u05d7 \u05d9\u05e9\u05e8\u05d0\u05dc\u05d9","rank":"\u05d2'\u05d9\u05dc\u05d8","answer":"\u05d3\u05d9\u05d5\u05e8","answers":["\u05d0\u05e1\u05ea\u05d9 \u05dc\u05d0\u05d5\u05d3\u05e8","\u05d4\u05d5\u05d5\u05d0\u05d9",4,0,1]},{"question":"\u05de\u05d4\u05d5 \u05e4\u05d3\u05d9\u05e7\u05d5\u05e8?","rank":"\u05d8\u05d9\u05e4\u05d5\u05dc \u05d1\u05e6\u05d9\u05e4\u05d5\u05e8\u05e0\u05d9\u05d9\u05dd \u05d1\u05e8\u05d2\u05dc\u05d9\u05d9\u05dd","answer":"\u05d8\u05d9\u05e4\u05d5\u05dc \u05d1\u05e6\u05d9\u05e4\u05d5\u05e8\u05e0\u05d9\u05d9\u05dd \u05d1\u05d9\u05d3\u05d9\u05d9\u05dd","answers":["\u05d8\u05d9\u05e4\u05d5\u05dc \u05d1\u05d2\u05d1\u05d5\u05ea","\u05d8\u05d9\u05e4\u05d5\u05dc \u05d1\u05e2\u05d9\u05e0\u05d9\u05d9\u05dd",1,0,1]},{"question":"\u05de\u05d4 \u05de\u05d4\u05d1\u05d0\u05d9\u05dd \u05d0\u05d9\u05e0\u05d5 \u05e9\u05d9\u05d9\u05da \u05dc\u05d0\u05d9\u05e4\u05d5\u05e8 \u05e2\u05d9\u05e0\u05d9\u05d9\u05dd?","rank":"\u05de\u05e1\u05e7\u05e8\u05d4","answer":"\u05e6\u05dc\u05dc\u05d9\u05ea","answers":["\u05ea\u05d5\u05d7\u05dd","\u05d0\u05d9\u05d9\u05dc\u05d9\u05e0\u05e8",3,0,1]},{"question":"laka \u05d4\u05d9\u05d0?","rank":"\u05e7\u05d5\u05e1\u05de\u05d8\u05d9\u05e7\u05d0\u05d9\u05d5\u05ea \u05e2\u05d3 \u05d4\u05d1\u05d9\u05ea","answer":"\u05e8\u05e9\u05ea \u05de\u05e0\u05d9\u05e7\u05d5\u05e8 \u05d0\u05e7\u05e1\u05e4\u05e8\u05e1","answers":["\u05de\u05db\u05d5\u05df \u05dc\u05dc\u05d9\u05de\u05d5\u05d3 \u05de\u05e8\u05d9\u05d7\u05ea \u05dc\u05e7\u05d9\u05dd","\u05dc\u05e7 \u05de\u05e8 \u05dc\u05de\u05e0\u05d9\u05e2\u05ea \u05db\u05e1\u05d9\u05e1\u05ea \u05e6\u05d9\u05e4\u05d5\u05e8\u05e0\u05d9\u05d9\u05dd",2,0,1]},{"question":"\u05de\u05d4 \u05de\u05d4\u05d1\u05d0\u05d9\u05dd \u05d0\u05d9\u05e0\u05d5 \u05e7\u05e9\u05d5\u05e8 \u05dc\u05ea\u05d7\u05d5\u05dd \u05e2\u05d9\u05e6\u05d5\u05d1 \u05e9\u05d9\u05e2\u05e8?","rank":"\u05d1\u05d9\u05d9\u05d1\u05d9\u05dc\u05d9\u05e1","answer":"\u05d2\u05d5\u05d5\u05e0\u05d9\u05dd","answers":["\u05e4\u05d9\u05e0\u05e6\u05d8\u05d4","\u05e8\u05d5\u05dc\u05d9\u05dd",3,0,1]},{"question":"\u05d4\u05d9\u05db\u05df \u05de\u05d9\u05d5\u05e6\u05e8 \u05e9\u05de\u05e4\u05d5 '\u05e4\u05e0\u05d8\u05df'?","rank":"\u05d0\u05e8\u05e6\u05d5\u05ea \u05d4\u05d1\u05e8\u05d9\u05ea","answer":"\u05d2\u05e8\u05de\u05e0\u05d9\u05d4","answers":["\u05e6\u05e8\u05e4\u05ea ","\u05e9\u05d5\u05d5\u05d9\u05e5",4,0,2]},{"question":"\u05de\u05d4 \u05de\u05d4\u05d1\u05d0\u05d9\u05dd \u05d4\u05d9\u05e0\u05d5 \u05de\u05e1\u05e4\u05e8 \u05e9\u05dc \u05de\u05e7\u05d3\u05dd \u05d4\u05d2\u05e0\u05d4?","rank":10,"answer":30,"answers":[90,57,2,0,2]},{"question":"cover girl \u05d4\u05d9\u05e0\u05d5 \u05de\u05d5\u05ea\u05d2 \u05d4\u05de\u05d2\u05d9\u05e2 \u05de?","rank":"\u05d0\u05e8\u05e6\u05d5\u05ea \u05d4\u05d1\u05e8\u05d9\u05ea","answer":"\u05d9\u05e4\u05df","answers":["\u05e1\u05e4\u05e8\u05d3","\u05d0\u05e0\u05d2\u05dc\u05d9\u05d4",1,0,2]},{"question":"\u05de\u05d9 \u05de\u05d4\u05d1\u05d0\u05d5\u05ea \u05d4\u05d9\u05d0 \u05d4\u05e4\u05e8\u05d6\u05e0\u05d8\u05d5\u05e8\u05d9\u05ea \u05e9\u05dc \u05d0\u05d9\u05dc \u05de\u05e7\u05d9\u05d0\u05d6'?","rank":"\u05de\u05d9\u05e8\u05d9 \u05d1\u05d5\u05d4\u05d3\u05e0\u05d4","answer":"\u05dc\u05d9\u05e8\u05d6 \u05d3\u05e8\u05d5\u05e8","answers":["\u05d0\u05e1\u05ea\u05d9 \u05d2\u05d9\u05e0\u05d6\u05d1\u05d5\u05e8\u05d2","\u05d1\u05e8 \u05e8\u05e4\u05d0\u05dc\u05d9",3,0,2]},{"question":"\u05de\u05d4\u05d5 '\u05d8\u05d9\u05e4\u05d9 \u05dc\u05d0 \u05d8\u05d5\u05d1 \u05dc\u05e9\u05de\u05d9\u05e8\u05d4 \u05d5\u05d8\u05d9\u05e4\u05d5\u05d7 \u05d4\u05e9\u05d9\u05e2\u05e8?","rank":"\u05dc\u05d2\u05d6\u05d5\u05e8 \u05e7\u05e6\u05d5\u05d5\u05ea","answer":"\u05e9\u05d9\u05de\u05d5\u05e9 \u05e8\u05d1 \u05d1\u05de\u05d9\u05d9\u05d1\u05e9 \u05e9\u05d9\u05e2\u05e8","answers":["\u05dc\u05d0 \u05dc\u05d7\u05e4\u05d5\u05e3 \u05db\u05dc \u05d9\u05d5\u05dd","\u05e9\u05d9\u05de\u05d5\u05e9 \u05d1\u05de\u05e1\u05db\u05d4 \u05dc\u05e9\u05d9\u05e2\u05e8",2,0,2]},{"question":"\u05de\u05ea\u05d9 \u05d4\u05d5\u05e7\u05dd \u05d1\u05d9\u05ea \u05d4\u05e1\u05e4\u05e8 \u05dc\u05d0\u05d9\u05e4\u05d5\u05e8 '\u05d9\u05e8\u05d9\u05df \u05e9\u05d7\u05e3'?","rank":1990,"answer":1979,"answers":[1986,1995,3,0,2]},{"question":"\u05d4\u05d9\u05db\u05df \u05e0\u05d5\u05dc\u05d3 \u05d3\"\u05e8 \u05e4\u05d9\u05e9\u05e8?","rank":"\u05e6'\u05db\u05d9\u05d4","answer":"\u05d9\u05e9\u05e8\u05d0\u05dc","answers":["\u05e4\u05d5\u05dc\u05d9\u05df","\u05d0\u05e8\u05e6\u05d5\u05ea \u05d4\u05d1\u05e8\u05d9\u05ea",1,0,3]},{"question":"\u05de\u05d4 \u05d4\u05d4\u05d1\u05d3\u05dc \u05d1\u05d9\u05df \u05e7\u05e8\u05dd \u05e4\u05e0\u05d9\u05dd \u05dc\u05d9\u05d5\u05dd \u05d5\u05dc\u05dc\u05d9\u05dc\u05d4?","rank":"\u05d0\u05d9\u05df \u05d4\u05d1\u05d3\u05dc","answer":"\u05d1\u05e7\u05e8\u05dd \u05dc\u05d9\u05dc\u05d4 \u05d9\u05e9 \u05d9\u05d5\u05ea\u05e8 \u05e9\u05de\u05df","answers":["\u05d1\u05e7\u05e8\u05dd \u05d9\u05d5\u05dd \u05d9\u05e9 \u05d9\u05d5\u05ea\u05e8 \u05e9\u05de\u05df","\u05d1\u05e7\u05e8\u05dd \u05dc\u05d9\u05dc\u05d4 \u05d9\u05e9 \u05d9\u05d5\u05ea\u05e8 SPF",2,0,3]},{"question":"\u05de\u05d4 \u05de\u05d4\u05d1\u05d0\u05d9\u05dd \u05d0\u05d9\u05e0\u05d5 \u05e9\u05d9\u05d8\u05d4 \u05dc\u05d8\u05d9\u05e4\u05d5\u05dc \u05d1\u05e4\u05d9\u05dc\u05d9\u05e0\u05d2?","rank":"\u05dc\u05d9\u05d9\u05d6\u05e8","answer":"\u05e1\u05d9\u05d1\u05d5\u05df \u05d4\u05d2\u05d5\u05e3","answers":["\u05d8\u05d9\u05e4\u05d5\u05dc \u05db\u05d9\u05de\u05d9","\u05d3\u05d9\u05e7\u05d5\u05e8",4,0,3]},{"question":"\u05de\u05d4\u05df \u05ea\u05db\u05d5\u05e0\u05d5\u05ea\u05d9\u05d5 \u05d4\u05e7\u05d5\u05e1\u05de\u05d8\u05d9\u05d5\u05ea \u05e9\u05dc \u05d4\u05de\u05dc\u05e4\u05e4\u05d5\u05df?","rank":"\u05d8\u05d9\u05e4\u05d5\u05dc \u05d1\u05d9\u05d1\u05dc\u05d5\u05ea","answer":"\u05d8\u05d9\u05e4\u05d5\u05dc \u05d1\u05e4\u05e6\u05e2\u05d5\u05e0\u05d9\u05dd","answers":["\u05e2\u05d5\u05e8 \u05e7\u05d5\u05e8\u05df \u05d5\u05d7\u05dc\u05e7","\u05d0\u05d9\u05df \u05dc\u05d5",3,0,3]},{"question":"\u05d0\u05d9\u05dc\u05d5 \u05de\u05d4\u05e9\u05de\u05e0\u05d9\u05dd \u05d4\u05d1\u05d0\u05d9\u05dd \u05d4\u05db\u05d9 \u05e4\u05d7\u05d5\u05ea \u05de\u05ea\u05d0\u05d9\u05dd \u05dc\u05de\u05e8\u05d9\u05d7\u05d4 \u05e2\u05dc \u05d4\u05e2\u05d5\u05e8?","rank":"\u05e9\u05de\u05df \u05e7\u05d5\u05e8\u05e0\u05d9\u05ea","answer":"\u05e9\u05de\u05df \u05d6\u05e8\u05e2\u05d9 \u05e2\u05e0\u05d1\u05d9\u05dd","answers":["\u05e9\u05de\u05df \u05e0\u05d1\u05d8 \u05d7\u05d9\u05d8\u05d4","\u05e9\u05de\u05df \u05e0\u05e8 \u05d4\u05dc\u05d9\u05dc\u05d4",1,0,3]},{"question":"\u05d0\u05d9\u05dc\u05d5 \u05de\u05d4\u05d1\u05d0\u05d9\u05dd \u05d4\u05d5\u05d0 \u05dc\u05d0 \u05ea\u05e8\u05d5\u05e4\u05ea \u05e1\u05d1\u05ea\u05d0 \u05dc\u05d9\u05d5\u05d1\u05e9 \u05d1\u05e9\u05e4\u05ea\u05d9\u05d9\u05dd?","rank":"\u05e9\u05de\u05df \u05d6\u05d9\u05ea","answer":"\u05d0\u05dc\u05d5\u05d5\u05e8\u05d4","answers":["\u05dc\u05d9\u05e7\u05d5\u05e7 \u05d4\u05e9\u05e4\u05ea\u05d9\u05d9\u05dd","\u05d3\u05d1\u05e9",3,0,3]},{"question":"\u05d0\u05d9\u05d6\u05d5 \u05d7\u05d1\u05e8\u05d4 \u05de\u05d1\u05e6\u05e2\u05ea \u05e0\u05d9\u05e1\u05d5\u05d9\u05d9\u05dd \u05e2\u05dc \u05d1\u05e2\u05dc\u05d9 \u05d7\u05d9\u05d9\u05dd?","rank":"\u05d3\"\u05e8 \u05d4\u05d0\u05d5\u05e9\u05e7\u05d4","answer":"\u05d0\u05e0\u05d8\u05d5\u05e0\u05d9\u05dd","answers":["\u05dc\u05dc\u05d9\u05df","\u05d3\u05d0\u05d1",4,0,3]}]